你在幹什麼？
Hey, what are you doing?
老天，你看清楚了嗎？
Jesus. Did you get a good look?
我只看到藍色豐田房車
Blue Toyota Camry, that's all I saw.
- 是沃頓家的狗  - 天啊
-It's the Wartons' dog.  -Oh, man.
看來是沒救了
It's not gonna make it.
看他們在不在家
Go see if they're home.
不要緊
It's okay.
世上有兩種苦痛
There are two kinds of pain.
一種會讓你變得強壯
The sort of pain that makes you strong
另一種是無用的痛  只讓人煎熬
or useless pain,  the sort of pain that's only suffering.
我沒耐性應付無用的事物
I have no patience for useless things.
這種情況需要果斷的人
Moments like this require someone  who will act.
能為他人所不願為
Who will do the unpleasant thing,
做出必須要做的事
the necessary thing.
好了
There.
不會痛了
No more pain.
有人肇事逃逸  我真的感到很抱歉
It was a hit and run. I'm awfully sorry.
它一定又越過護欄
He must've jumped over the fence again.
聽著，史提夫會去報案  他會派人去追查
Look, Steve is gonna file a report on the car.  He'll put his people on it.
一定會把他們揪出來
We'll track them down.
好美
Stunning.
出發吧？
Shall we?
…3、2、1  ...three, two, one.
新年快樂！
Happy New Year!
總統當選人葛瑞沃克
President-elect Garrett Walker.
我喜歡他嗎？不喜歡
Do I like him? No.
信任他嗎？這不是重點
Do I believe in him? That's beside the point.
任何能贏得七千萬選票的政客
Any politician that gets 70 million votes
擁有的權勢大過於他本人
has tapped into something larger  than himself,
也大過於我，就算我不想承認
Iarger than even me,  as much as I hate to admit it.
看看那勝者的微笑  那充滿信任的眼神
Look at that winning smile,  those trusting eyes.
我早些時候就跟他搭上線  成為他的得力助手
I latched onto him early on  and made myselfvital.
在國會混了22年  我早摸清了局勢
After 22 years in Congress,  I can smell which way the wind is blowing.
吉姆馬修  他那剛正不阿的副總統
Jim Matthews,  his Right Honorable Vice President.
前賓州州長
Former governor of Pennsylvania.
他很稱職地拉攏了賓州的選民  願神眷顧他
He did his duty in delivering  the Keystone State, bless his heart.
他們這會卻打算扔下他
Now they're about to put him out to pasture.
但他看來還真快樂，不是嗎？
But he looks happy enough, doesn't he?
對某些人來說  位子的大小才是最重要的
For some, it's simply the size of the chair.
琳達瓦克斯，沃克的參謀  是我幫她謀得職位
Linda Vasquez, Walker's chief of staff.  I got her hired.
她是拉丁裔女人  但最重要的是
She's a woman, check. And a Latina, check.  But more important than that,
她夠強悍，符合所有的條件
she's as tough as a two-dollar steak.  Check, check, check.
想要入白宮  靠的可不只是大門鑰匙
When it comes to the White House, you not  only need the keys in your back-pocket,
還得找個看門人
you need the gatekeeper.
至於我，我只不過是個小小的  眾議院多數黨黨鞭
As for me,  I'm just the lowly House Majority Whip.
我負責在黨間鬥爭的國會中  推動議案
I keep things moving in a Congress  choked by pettiness and lassitude.
我的工作就是讓管道通暢
My job is to clear the pipes  and keep the sludge moving.
但我很快就不用通水管了
But I won't have to be a plumber  much longer.
我熬出頭了，跟對了老大
I've done my time. I've backed the right man.
有捨就有得
Give and take.
歡迎來到華府
Welcome to Washington.
你該去理髮了
You need a haircut.
是嗎？
You think?
稍微修一下
A little trim.
你到時要穿什麼？
What are you going to wear?
- 你是指會議嗎？  - 宣佈時
-You mean for the meeting?  -For the announcement.
我打算穿深藍色條紋那套
I'll wear my navy blue,  the one with the pinstripes.
很好，你穿那套西裝很帥氣
Good. You look handsome in that suit.
我不清楚他們會不會  在你的董事會開始前宣佈
I don't know if they'll announce  before your board meeting.
只要獻金不會停止就好
As long as I can say the donation is coming.
只要正式宣佈  善可工業就會開支票給你
Soon as it's official,  SanCorp will write you a check.
今年對我們將是重要的一年
This is going to be a big year for us.
- 我想要從這裏開始  - 所以我才在這
-I wanna start with something here.  -That's why I'm here.
真的？什麼呢？
Really? What?
我想應該與移民  銀行或教育相關吧
I'd say immigration, banking or education.
但我以往的線民都沒法確認消息
But none of my regular sources  can confirm that.
是因為不知道  還是他們不肯透露？
Because they don't know,  or because they're not talking?
因為他們不知道
Because they don't know.
繼續跟，總得挖出些什麼
Keep at it. Get me something.
抱歉，翰默史密先生  我是喬伊
Sorry. Sorry, Mr. Hammerschmidt. Zoe.
- 邦斯  - 沒錯
-Barnes.  -Right.
他是否花了一年才記住你的名字？
Did it take him a year  to remember your name?
更長
Longer.
早安，盧卡斯
Good morning, Lucas.
有何貴幹，喬伊？
What can I do for you, Zoe?
我真是受夠了費郡的郡議會
I am sick of the Fairfax County Council.
你天天這麼說
You tell me every day.
讓我上線吧
Move me online.
我自己的部落格
My own blog.
第一人稱、主觀性、五百字
First person. Subjective. 500 words.
- 辦不到  - 我可以移居幕後
-Not gonna happen.  -I'll go underground.
在後面的小房間裏，廁所裏
Back rooms, the urinals.
讓我去說服國會的人
I'll win over staff members on the Hill.
- 他們都需要地方發洩  - 八卦專欄
-They need a place to vent.  -A gossip column.
不，我們掀開面紗
No. We lift the veil.
揭發事實
What's really going on.
我們可是《華府先軀報》  喬伊，不是壹電視
This is The Washington Herald, Zoe,  it's not TMZ.
- 你知道有多少人看壹電視嗎？  - 我才不在乎
-Do you know how many people watch TMZ?  -I couldn't care less.
正因此傳統報紙才快混不下去
Which is why print journalism is dying.
要死也要死得有尊嚴  至少這家報社是如此
Then it'll die with dignity.  At least at this paper.
你還卡在上個世紀，盧卡斯  你缺乏想像力
You're stuck in the 20th century, Lucas.  You lack imagination.
或許吧，但我現在不需要想像力  我需要的是銷售量
Maybe so, but right now,  I don't need imagination, I need copy.
晚上與週末是你的自由
Your nights and weekends are yours.
我很支持你想做的
I applaud whatever you want to do,
只要不是在上班時間
as long as it's not on my time.
- 你是要我回去工作  - 我是
-You're telling me to get back to work.  -I am.
其實是要我別再煩你
What you're really telling me is to fuck off.
兩者都是
I'm telling you both.
是普倫斯基金會的查普曼先生
It's Mr. Chapman, already,  from Province Trust.
幫我擋電話，克裏絲汀娜
Hold my calls, Christina.
亨利
Henry.
你好
It's good to see you.
- 這次待多久？  - 就今天
-How long are you in town for?  -Just today.
就職典禮時你一定要來
You gotta come back down  for the inauguration.
我能讓你入場
I can hook you up.
不如在區劃法給我行個方便
How about you hook me up  with the zoning laws
你答應要改的？
you promised to get changed?
我們有一千兩百萬托管  一塊沒法破土的空地
We've got 12 million sitting in escrow  for an empty lot we can't build on.
我明白，但你得知道  這是市政府的問題
I know. But you gotta understand,  it's a local municipal issue.
- 我可沒法拿起電話…  - 不能嗎？
-I can't just pick up the phone...  -You can't?
因為你跟我們要五萬獻金時  可不是這麼說的
Because that's not what you led us to believe  when you begged for 50 grand in donations.
沒錯
Right.
等等
One sec.
克裏絲汀娜，我說過別接進來  別打擾我與查普曼先生
Christina, I said no calls.  Not while I'm meeting with Mr. Chapman.
總統當選人？
The President-elect?
不好意思
Do you mind?
不，請接
No, go ahead, please.
接進來，克裏絲汀娜
Put him through, Christina.
總統當選人先生
Mr. President-elect.
謝謝，沒錯，我們…  很高興以雙位數領先獲選
Thank you. Yes, we were...  We were pleased to win by double digits.
當然，只要您有需要
Absolutely, anything you need.
我需要你將你那三寸不爛之舌  伸入我大腿中間
I need you to put your long, wet,  talented tongue between my thighs
讓我像莫妮卡一樣呻吟…
and make me squeal like Monica...
我也是
Me too, me too.
好的，謝謝您
Okay. Thank you, sir.
抱歉，剛說到哪？
I'm so sorry. Where were we?
沃克，這人怎樣？
Walker, what's he like?
總統當選人遲到了嗎？
Is the President-elect running late?
他無法趕到  我會再向他匯報的
No. He couldn't make it. I'll brief him, though.
好吧
Okay.
這是我寫的公文
This is the memo I drafted
我們正在構思的中東政策
on our Middle East policy  we've been developing.
我想要引用雷根
Now, I wanna borrow from Reagan,
發明一個新詞「滴流外交」
I'd like to coin the phrase  "trickle-down diplomacy."
- 這麼一來…  - 法蘭，容我先打個岔
-That way...  -Frank, I'm going to stop you there.
我們並未打算提名你  出任國務卿
We're not nominating you  for Secretary of State.
我知道他承諾過你  但現在情勢有所變化
I know he made you a promise,  but circumstances have changed.
琳達，所謂承諾
The nature of promises, Linda,
就表示不受情勢變化所影響
is that they remain immune  to changing circumstances.
葛瑞斟酌了很久
Garrett has thought long  and hard about this,
他認為我們比較需要你身處國會
and he's decided we need you  to stay in Congress.
什麼時候下的決定？
When was this decision made?
為何完全沒有經過我？
And why wasn't I part of a conversation?
抱歉，我若作得了主
I'm sorry, Frank. If it had been up to me,
就不會等到現在才告訴你
I wouldn't have waited this long to tell you.
所以老早就打算這麼做
So you knew you were going to do this.
一直都有在談
It has been an evolving discussion.
這是個沒膽的決定
It's a chicken-shit move.
- 法蘭…  - 我受過審查
-Frank...  -I was vetted.
- 也是做樣子？  - 不
-Was that a ruse?  -No.
聽清楚了
Let's be absolutely clear.
少了我根本不可能勝選
You wouldn't have won without me.
沒錯，但我們必須要領導  這代表要做些困難的決定
You're right. But now we have to lead,  and that means making tough choices.
你也知道  教育這塊對我們來說是首要
As you know,  education is a top priority for us.
整體的大改革
A complete federal overhaul.
不只是教育，法蘭  國會分裂得很厲害
But it's not just education, Frank.  Congress is split.
你在那的重要性比在國務院高
We need you there more than we need you  in the State Department.
你當初可是我僱用的，琳達
I got you hired, Linda.
- 我知道  - 獻金、背書
-I know.  -Donations, endorsements.
整個競選的外交政策都是我寫的
I wrote the campaign's  entire foreign policy platform.
多年外交委員會的經驗…
I bring years of foreign affairs committee...
法蘭，拜託你
Frank, please.
我要親自跟沃克談
I wanna speak to Walker personally.
這已成定案了
The decision is made.
我們需要你，法蘭
We need you, Frank.
你願不願意跟我們同一陣線？
Will you stand beside us or not?
當然，若這是總統的意思
Of course. If that's what the President wants.
很高興聽到你這麼說
I'm very glad to hear that.
我很好奇，不是我是誰？
I'm curious. If not me, then who?
麥克凱恩
Michael Kern.
是個很好的人選
Well, that is an excellent choice.
淨水創權
能再清楚一點嗎？
Can we make it more clear?
我只是要確定不會讓人覺得  我們忽略了國內的…
I just want to make sure it doesn't look like  we're neglecting our domestic...
不，我的意思是  我們在擴大任務範圍
No. No, no, no. I'm gonna say  that we're expanding our mission.
好的
Okay.
我們打算請另一個組織  來協助我們
And we're bringing on a new organization  to help us.
- 知道要找哪一個了嗎？  - 還有幾個要看的，但是…
-Do you know which one yet?  -I'm still looking into a few options, but...
告訴我，我們的協議是什麼  可以聘請多少人？
Tell me, what did we agree on,  that we could hire how many new people?
- 六名嗎？  - 六、七名吧
-Six?  -Six, maybe seven.
夠啦
We'll have enough.
真令人興奮
It's exciting.
我們的新方向
This new direction we're heading.
只是不知道這麼多人要塞哪裏
I just don't know where we're going to fit  all the people.
是否該擴展空間？
Do you think we have to look  into additional space?
不，我來想法子
No, no, no, no. I'll find a way.
好吧，記得修改報表
Okay, so make the changes  to the PowerPoint
我們2點半再開一次會
and let's meet again at 2:30.
好
Okay.
是我
It's me.
這樣留言感覺好白癡
I feel like an idiot leaving messages like this.
回我電話
Call me back.
華府先驅報
怎麼了，喬伊？
What is it, Zoe?
我知道你在忙白宮的事
I know you're going to have your hands full  at the White House,
若需要幫忙查資料  還是一些幕後工作…
so if you need someone to do research  or punch out background...
應該沒問題
I think I'll be fine.
若太忙了，或是需要幫忙
Well, if things get hectic,  and you need any help.
好讓你在部落格  寫說你跟大人物們共事？
So you can blog about rubbing shoulders  with the big boys?
盧卡斯告訴你什麼？
What did Lucas tell you?
我無冒犯之意，喬伊  但我沒時間帶小孩
Look, no offense, Zoe, but I don't have time  to be anyone's training wheels.
我只是覺得…
I just thought...
不，我其實是向你伸出援手
No, I was actually offering to lend a hand.
- 沒錯  - 知道了，謝了
-That's it.  -Got it. Thanks.
克萊兒，下午4點58分  你在哪裏？
- 克萊兒…  - 你沒回我
-Claire...  -You didn't call.
- 我剛才…  - 你沒回我電話，法蘭斯
-I was...  -You didn't call me, Francis.
九個小時，你沒打給我
Nine hours. You don't not call me.
這麼大的事
Not when it's this big.
你說得對
You're right.
我們什麼時候開始躲避對方了？
When have we ever avoided each other?
我想先找到解決之道
I wanted a solution first.
- 找到了嗎？  - 還沒
-Do you have one?  -Not yet.
這也影響到我，法蘭斯
This affects me too, Francis.
我不是為錢的事生氣
And it's not the money I'm upset about.
我們是共同體
It's that we do things together.
當你將我排除在外  我們就像自由落體
When you don't involve me, we're in free fall.
我應該要打給你的  但是我沒有
I should have called you and I didn't.
發生什麼事了？
What happened?
她說他們需要我留在國會
She says they need to keep me in Congress.
琳達這麼說？
Linda said that?
沃克根本不在場
Walker wasn't even there.
這才是我最氣的地方  他連正眼看我的勇氣都沒有…
That's what really gets me. He didn't have  the courage to look me in the eye...
就知道那女人不可信
I knew you shouldn't trust that woman.
我沒有，我誰都沒相信
I didn't. I don't. I don't trust anyone.
那你怎麼會沒料到這招？
Then how could you not see this coming?
我沒想到他們有這能耐
I never thought they were capable.
你通常不會低估人的  法蘭斯
You don't usually  underestimate people, Francis.
我知道
I know.
狂妄，野心
Hubris. Ambition.
- 你該生氣  - 我氣壞了
-You should be angry.  -I'm livid.
有嗎？我怎麼沒感覺到
Then where is that? I don't see it.
你要我怎麼做？
What do you want me to do?
鬼喊鬼叫嗎？鬧脾氣？
Scream and yell? Throw a tantrum?
至少比現在激動  你豈止這點能耐，法蘭斯
I want more than I'm seeing.  You're better than this, Francis.
對不起，克萊兒
Well, I'm sorry, Claire.
對不起
I am sorry.
不，我不接受
No. That I won't accept.
- 什麼？  - 道歉
-What?  -Apologies.
我丈夫絕不會道歉  對我也不會
My husband doesn't apologize, even to me.
你起來多久了？
How long have you been up?
好幾個小時了
Hours.
我知道該怎麼做了
I know what I have to do.
很好
Good.
以後會有很多像這樣的夜晚
We'll have a lot of nights like this,
策劃，沒得睡
making plans, very little sleep.
我早料到是這樣  這點我不擔心
I expected that. That doesn't worry me.
我該去上班了
I better get to work.
我幫你把西裝拿出來了
I laid a suit out for you upstairs.
深藍色的那套
The navy blue one.
我愛這女人  比鯊魚嗜血還要愛
I love that woman.  I love her more than sharks love blood.
新聞特報  凱恩提名國務卿
你覺得為什麼選他？
Why do you think they went with him?
我們太稱職了  他們沒法讓我們離開國會
We're too good.  They can't afford to lose us in Congress.
他有進場維修  下巴有拉皮吧，一定有染髮
He's had work done. A chin tuck probably.  He definitely dyes his hair.
我們該說什麼嗎？
Do we say anything?
不，千萬不要，除非他自己提
No. God, no. Not unless he brings it up.
南茜？
Nancy?
- 9點25分…  - 取消所有行程
-9:25...  -Cancel everything.
史坦普，跟我走
Stamper, you're with me.
聽著…
Now, look...
他們幫了我們大忙，道格
They've done us a great favor, Doug.
我們不再有聯盟的束縛
We are no longer bound by allegiances.
不為任何人效力
We serve no one.
我們只遵循一個法則
We live by one rule and one rule only,
就是再也不要處於這樣的處境
never again will we allow ourselves  to be put in such a position.
沃克與瓦克斯
Walker and Vasquez.
他們所有人，全部都得負責
All of them. I hold them all accountable.
- 報復？  - 不
-Retribution?  -No.
不，不只這樣
No. It's more than that.
往後退一步
Take a step back.
看看全局
Look at the bigger picture.
我想我明白你的意思了  第一個就是凱恩嗎？
I think I see what you're getting at.  Kern first?
想要吞鯨就得這樣，道格  一口口蠶食它
That's how you devour a whale, Doug.  One bite at a time.
你會選誰出任國務卿？
Who would you want?  For Secretary of State?
給我個名單  不管我們採取什麼行動
Give me a list of choices.  And however we do this,
都需要緩衝
we'll also need a buffer.
- 你是指跑腿小弟？  - 對
-You mean an errand boy?  -Yes.
一個我們能全然掌控的人
Somebody we control completely.
- 我會留意風聲的  - 很好
-I'll keep my ear to the ground.  -Good.
我從昨天起就沒吃
I haven't eaten since yesterday.
我幾乎覺得他很可憐
I almost pity him.
他不是自願被犧牲
He didn't choose to be put on my platter.
當我讓他屍骨無存拿去餵狗
When I carve him up  and toss him to the dogs,
他到時才無法逃避現實
only then will he confront  that brutal, inescapable truth.
「天啊，原來我從頭到尾  都被當廚餘」
"My God,  all I ever amounted to was chitlins."
「自我降卑者必將高舉」
"And he that shall humble himself  shall be exalted."
馬太福音23章12節
Matthew 23:1 2.
感謝主
Thanks be to God.
我今天要講的是謙卑
I'd like to speak today  on the subject of humility.
你們當中許多人剛連任
A lot ofyou have just won re-election.
若沒有就不會坐在這
Ifyou hadn't, you might not be sitting here.
我們當然應該享受成功  心懷感恩
And of course, we should enjoy our success,  and be grateful for it.
但千萬別讓感恩變質成驕傲
But never let your gratitude sour into pride.
在未來幾年  你們將面臨各種挑戰
You'll have many challenges ahead  over the next couple of years.
一個人的人格無法取決於  他如何享受勝利
And a person's character isn't determined  by how he or she enjoys victory,
而是在於他如何承受失敗
but rather how he or she endures defeat.
信仰是抵擋黑暗時期的最佳武器
Nothing can help us endure dark times  better than our faith.
- 克萊兒  - 你好，費莉絲
-Claire.  -Hello, Felicity.
- 你好嗎？  - 很好，你呢？
-How are you?  -Good. How are you?
很好，那件事真抱歉  這樣真的很不對
Good. I'm sorry about that.  It's just not right.
查理斯和我都搞不懂  沃克在想什麼
Charles and I can't understand  what Walker was thinking.
很感謝你  但說真的，我偷偷跟你說
That's very sweet of you,  but really, between you and me,
我覺得法蘭斯反而鬆了口氣
I think Francis is relieved.
他其實比較習慣在國會
He just feels much more at home  in Congress.
我本來還想賭一百萬  他們一定選你
I would've bet a million dollars  they were going to pick you.
還好你有一百萬身家可以輸
Well, it's a good thing  you have a million dollars to spare.
但你根本是不二人選
But you are by far and away the only choice.
我很感謝你這麼想
I appreciate you saying that.
麥克？拜託
I mean, Michael? Come on.
- 他的資歷還不及你一半…  - 葛瑞是個聰明人
-He's got half the experience you do...  -Garrett is a smart man.
他知道自己在做什麼
He knows what he's doing.
你的氣量比我大多了，法蘭
You're a bigger man than l, Frank.
你要喝點酒嗎？
You want some of that wine?
當然要
Yes, definitely.
這可是好酒，你哪弄來的？
Man, this is some good shit.  Where did you get it?
我從發言人派對的貴賓室摸來的
I kind of lifted it from the VlP room  ofthe Speakers' holiday party.
真令人佩服  20年的波多爾紅酒
I'm impressed. Bordeaux, 20 years old.
配你剛好
It seemed about right for you.
為什麼這麼說？
Why would you say that to me?
我快30了  這對你來說幾乎是古人
I'm almost 30.  That's practically ancient in your book.
- 我才沒有年齡歧視  - 是嗎？
-I don't discriminate when it comes to age.  -Really?
你上次僱用年過40的人是何時？
When's the last time you hired  a 40-year-old staffer?
這不代表我不會
Doesn't mean I wouldn't.
只要她床上功夫夠厲害
As long as she's good in the sack.
- 別這樣  - 不是嗎？
-Come on.  -Well, it's true, isn't it?
為什麼要這樣？
Where's this coming from?
你不會為了瓦薩畢業的小騷貨  就甩了我嗎？
You're not gonna just toss me aside  for some slut straight out ofVassar?
所以你是要談這個
So we're having that conversation.
已經半年了  這可不是隨便玩玩而已
It's been six months.  It's not a little office fling anymore.
你想要逼我講出那幾個字
You want me to say those three magic words.
其中一個是愛
One of which starts with an L.
好吧，我說就是了
Okay, I'll say 'em.
克裏絲汀娜葛蘭格
Christina Gallagher,
愛死我的鳥蛋
Iick my balls.
天啊…你這混蛋
Oh, my... You're a bastard.
我愛你
I love you.
我愛你，克裏絲汀娜
I love you, Christina.
我愛你
I love you.
現在願意給鳥蛋們一些愛嗎？
Now will you lick my balls?
我很好奇我們究竟是贊助人  捐助人還是麻瘋病人？
So I'm curious.  Are we patrons, benefactors or lepers?
信不信由你，我們是天使
Believe it or not, we're angels.
我去外面假裝講手機
I'm gonna go outside  and pretend to use my cell phone.
去吧
Go.
國家表演藝術中心
- 可以借你的外套嗎？  - 可以
-Can I have your jacket?  -Yeah.
好
Okay.
你要上床了嗎？
Are you coming to bed?
我再待一下
I'll be up in a bit.
- 別熬夜了  - 好，我馬上就過去
-Don't stay up all night.  -No, I'll be right there.
謝謝你，我會再打給你的
Thanks so much. I'll call you.
等等，我還以為今晚很愉快
Wait. I thought you had a good time.
是啊，我很喜歡  我從來沒去過那裏
I did. I loved it. I've never been before.
或許我該上來坐坐
Well, maybe I could come up.
布萊恩，你人真的很好
Brian, you're so sweet. Really.
但若我想跟你上床  你不可能不知道的
But if I was going to fuck you, you'd know.
真的很謝謝你
Thanks so much.
想要他們重視你  或許不該只穿條丁字褲？
法蘭斯安德沃議員
美國眾議院多數黨黨鞭
他看來挺嚴肅的
- 她來了  - 讓她進來
-She's here.  -Send her in.
總統參謀來國會倒是挺少見的
It's quite rare for a president's chief of staff  to climb the Hill.
可能是來拜碼頭  不然就是走投無路
A gesture of respect, no doubt,  or desperation.
我猜她會推唐納布萊斯  出任教育部長
I'm guessing she'll say  Donald Blythe for Education.
來看我是否猜對了
Let's see if I'm right.
早安，琳達
Good morning, Linda.
很感謝你親自跑來
Thank you so much for making the trip up.
當然，我很樂意
Of course. My pleasure.
教育？
Education?
首先
First things first.
這是就職典禮的座席圖
The seating chart for the inauguration.
你與克萊兒坐這可以嗎？
How do these two work for you and Claire?
哇
Wow.
還包括兩張傑弗遜晚宴的入場券
They come with a complimentary set  of tickets to the Jefferson Ball.
克萊兒一定會樂翻天
Claire will be over the moon.
很好，我很高興
Good, I'm so glad.
再來，教育部
So, education.
我們請唐納布萊斯草擬提案
We have Donald Blythe  drafting the legislation.
- 唐納布萊斯？老天  - 我知道
-Donald Blythe? Jesus.  -I know.
所以你們打算推出共產提案？
So you want a bill  just two steps left of Karl Marx?
我建議總統當選人別支持  但唐納是教育的招牌
I advised the President-elect against it,  but Donald is the face of education.
他推改革已經25年了
He's been pushing reform for 25 years.
你要我將他拉回中間？
You want me to guide him to the middle.
我們需要一個能通過的提案
We need a bill we can pass.
我是否能全權處理？
Do I have absolute autonomy  and authority on this?
還有一件事
There's more.
葛瑞希望提案  在他上任百日內就能決議
Garrett wants the bill on the floor  in the first 100 days.
他希望能在就職時做出承諾
He wants to make a pledge  in his inaugural address.
那…
That's...
很有野心，琳達
That's very ambitious, Linda.
辦得到嗎？
Can we make that pledge?
百日內？
A hundred days?
我可以
I can deliver.
有消息通知我
Keep me posted.
我去跟唐納談  下禮拜跟你連絡
I'll talk with Donald.  I'll check in with you later in the week.
太好了
Terrific.
聞到了嗎？
Did you smell that?
裝模作樣？虛假的味道？
The smugness? The false deference?
她以為兩張入場券就能收買我  當我是誰啊？
She thinks I can be bought  with a pair of tickets. What am l?
二戰後身處柏林的妓女  看著絲襪與巧克力流口水嗎？
A whore in post-war Berlin salivating  over free stockings and chocolate?
她所要求的代價可不只這些
What she's asking  will cost far more than that.
- 弗格森？  - 太老
-Ferguson?  -Too old.
- 威利？  - 太蠢
-Willis?  -Too stupid.
- 波伊？  - 太娘
-Boyd?  -Too queer.
真的？
Really?
他已婚還有三個孩子
He's married with three kids.
- 要讓他們知道還得了  - 好吧
-And wouldn't they be devastated.  -All right.
那凱薩琳杜倫呢？
What about Catherine Durant?
凱西杜倫，她公然反對沃克
Cathy Durant. She was vocally anti-Walker.
經驗也夠
She's got the experience.
跟她約個時間吧
Set up a meeting.
你好
Hey.
善可的獻金呢？
The donation from SanCorp?
我們得另覓金主
The money will have to come  from somewhere else.
發生什麼事？
What happened?
我重看了一下2013年的預算
I've looked over the budget for fiscal '13
當中有160萬是薪資支出
and we've allocated $1.6 million for salaries.
這數字需要減半
We need to cut that in half.
- 你的意思是…  - 艾薇琳，我們得解雇一些人
-You're suggesting...  -Evelyn, we're going to let some people go.
這可會裁掉一半的人員
That would be half of our staff.
我們必須騰出些資金
We have to carve out some room.
你這樣會解雇許多  一開始就跟著我們的人
You would have to fire some essential people  who have been with us since the beginning.
我們是慈善機構  但不是針對我們的員工
We are a charity, but not for our employees.
克萊兒，對於國際化這件事  我一直都不願說什麼
You know, Claire, I've held my tongue about  this whole international thing for a while,
但我真的不懂
but I don't get it.
我們經營得很成功
We are really good at what we do.
為什麼非要強迫自己轉型呢？
Why do we have to try  and be something we're not?
因為我們遇到瓶頸，艾薇琳
Because we've plateaued, Evelyn.
我們這整個組織都應該…
And it is time for us,  for our entire organization...
但是去非洲挖井？  我們根本不瞭解這塊
But digging wells in Africa?  We don't know anything about that.
所以才需要新血
Which is why  we have to bring in new people.
我已經向董事會這麼建議  我們將會朝這個方向走
This is the plan that I've proposed to the  board and we are moving forward with it.
請列張名單給我
I'd like a list of names, please.
克萊兒，要不要再考慮一下？
Claire, can we just think about this?
我已經深思熟慮過了
I have thought about it.  I've put a lot of thought into it.
- 但我認為…  - 艾薇琳，你身為行政主管
-But I think...  -Evelyn, you're the office manager.
我需要你信任我
I need you to trust  that I know what I'm doing.
請盡快將名單給我
So please get me that list  as soon as possible.
- 女士，你不能上去  - 抱歉
-Ma'am. You can't go up.  -I'm sorry.
- 我就問一個問題  - 不行
-I just have one question.  -No. No.
- 很抱歉，這女人…  - 議員
-Sir, I apologize, this woman...  -Congressman.
- 小姐，麻煩你退後  - 我只需要一分鐘
-Miss, you need to step away from the door.  -lf I could just have one second.
你是誰？
Who are you?
我叫喬伊邦斯  是《華府先軀報》的記者
My name is Zoe Barnes.  I'm a reporter at the Washington Herald.
現在已經過晚上10點半  這裏是我家
It is after 10:30 at night and this is my home.
- 我不允許…  - 我們都喜歡攀高附貴
-I do not allow...  -We're part of a mutual admiration society.
你也愛聽交響樂
You're a fan of the symphony.
我比較喜歡觀察人
More for the people-watching than the music.
不要緊，史提夫  進來吧，邦斯小姐
It's all right, Steve. Come on in, Ms. Barnes.
很烈
It's strong.
你喜歡喝淡一點嗎？
You'd prefer it weak?
不，越烈越好
No, the stronger the better.
看一眼又不會少塊肉
There's no harm in looking.
這是很不入流的把戲
That's a cheap ploy.
雖不入流確很有效
It's cheap but effective.
你確實是引起我的注意了
Well, you certainly have  my undivided attention.
很好，我之所以登門拜訪…
Good, the reason I'm here...
前戲結束了嗎？
Is foreplay over?
我好像在哪讀過  甘迺迪撐不過三分鐘
I read somewhere that JFK never lasted  more than three minutes.
重點是？
The point being?
時間寶貴
Time is precious.
有權勢的人沒時間搞前戲
Powerful people  don't have the luxury of foreplay.
好吧，有何貴幹，邦斯小姐？
Okay. So why are you here, Ms. Barnes?
我需要找個人聊聊
I need somebody I can talk to.
我們不就在聊  是要聊什麼呢？
We're talking.  Tell me what we're talking about.
你的身份保密  你說什麼我就登什麼
I protect your identity,  I print whatever you tell me.
我絕不多問
And I'll never ask any questions.
你憑什麼認為  我沒跟你的其他同事
And what makes you think  I don't already have such an arrangement
達成同樣協議？
with one of your colleagues?
若有的話  你就不會放我進來了
Because if you did,  you wouldn't have let me through the door.
在我漫長成功的生涯中  一直避免跟媒體有這種曖昧關係
I've led a very long, very successful career  avoiding this sort of intrigue with the press.
現在好像也沒什麼好處
I can't see any advantage in starting now.
但有什麼壞處嗎？
But is there any disadvantage?
首先，拖泥帶水
Sloppiness, for one.
我保證會全然保密
I promise you absolute discretion.
那我們就是在談信任了
So we're talking about trust.
隨便你想用什麼措辭
Use whatever word you like.
措辭可是很重要的，邦斯小姐
Words matter very much, Ms. Barnes.
就以你的職業來說  更應該注重這點
You should care more about them,  given your profession.
沒錯，你的信任
Then yes, your trust.
那我究竟該相信  哪一個喬伊邦斯？
So which Zoe Barnes am I to trust?
是報導消防員  娶了開單女員警的那個？
The one who wrote about the fireman  that married the meter maid?
還是洋洋灑灑寫了  石溪公園跑步道報導的那個？
Or the one who authored a very fine article  on a new jogging path in Rock Creek Park.
別得意了，我什麼都讀
Don't be flattered. I read everything.
他們對我可是大材小用
I'm better than what they have me doing.
- 你明白那種感受  - 是嗎？
-You know what that feels like.  -Do l?
你本來可以是個傑出的國務卿
You would have made  a great Secretary of State.
我究竟能怎麼幫你，邦斯小姐？
How exactly may I help you, Ms. Barnes?
你一定知道總統府的立法議程
You must know  the administration's legislative agenda.
- 要先推什麼  - 或許
-What's coming up first.  -I may.
能告訴我嗎？
Will you tell me?
你認為是什麼？
What would be your guess?
- 教育  - 為什麼？
-Education.  -Why?
移民法太具爭議  稅法改革不夠引人注目
Immigration is too controversial.  Tax-reform isn't sexy enough.
所有人都會挺小孩子
Everyone can get behind children.
是教育嗎？
Is it education?
你是可以這麼想  我不予置評
You might very well think that.  I couldn't possibly comment.
給個提示吧
A hint.
- 很晚了，邦斯小姐  - 可以再跟你聊嗎？
-It's late, Ms. Barnes.  -Can we talk again?
我希望你能體諒  我需要睡一覺明天再說
I hope you'll understand  that I want to sleep on all this.
我從不在大半夜做重大決定
I never make such big decisions  so long after sunset and so far from dawn.
後面有我手機號碼
My cell phone's on the back.
你有將邦斯小姐  納入訪客名單嗎？
Did you put Ms. Barnes  in the visitors' ledger?
- 還沒  - 不要
-Not yet.  -Don't.
- 不用多說  - 不用多說
-Needless to say.  -Needless.
你好
Hello.
克萊兒，這位是  《華府先軀報》的邦斯小姐
Claire, this is Ms. Zoe Barnes,  of the Washington Herald.
她正要走了
She was just leaving.
幸會，安德沃夫人
Very nice to meet you, Mrs. Underwood.
小心開車，路上都結冰了
Drive safe. There's a lot of ice on the road.
我會的，謝謝你
I will. Thank you.
- 那招對誰都有用嗎？  - 哪招？
-Does that work on anybody?  -Does what?
集中托高胸罩配V領上衣？
The push-up bra and the V-neck tee?
我可不知道對誰管用
Well, if it does, I don't know who they are.
好，放輕鬆
Okay. Relax, relax.
- 駕照與汽車登記證  - 在置物箱裏，甜心
-License and registration.  -The glove compartment, sweetheart.
這不是你的駕照  是星巴克的儲值卡
This isn't your driver's license.  It's a Starbucks card.
該死，抱歉
Oh, shit. Sorry.
先生，你有飲酒嗎？
Sir, have you been drinking?
沒有，我這時候從不喝咖啡
No, I never drink coffee at this hour.
請你下車
I'm going to need you to step out of the car.
- 我若超速你可以開我單…  - 先生，請馬上下車
-lf I was speeding, you can write me a ticket...  -Sir, step out of the car right now.
我不想要顯官威  但我可是國會成員
Look, I don't want to be a prick,  but I'm a member of Congress.
你就算是中國國王我也不管
I don't care if you're the King of China.
中國沒有國王
China doesn't have a king.
中國是共產制度…
It's a communist ogliwarchy...
快下車，你也是，甜心
Let's go. Out. You too, sweetie.
該死，這字真難念
Fuck, that is hard to say.
喂？
Hello?
好，保他出來
Good. Well, let's get him out.
介意我加入嗎？
Mind if I join you?
現在是怎樣？
What the fuck is going on?
- 我以為跟我會面的是…  - 是我
-I thought I was meeting...  -No. You're meeting me.
現在凌晨4點耶  我的市政會會議…
It's 4:00 in the goddamn morning.  I've got a city council meeting in...
你當警察局長有十年了吧？
You've been police commissioner for what,  almost a decade now?
我們來這是要聊我的履歷？
We're here to talk about my resume?
履歷上加個華府市長  應該會很漂亮吧？
Mayor of D.C. would look good  on that resume, wouldn't it?
我們知道你早有意圖競選
We know that you've been angling to run  for some time.
經驗是你的優勢
Experience is your strong suit.
但找人背書和募款  不是你的強項
Endorsement and fundraising are not.
我們能協助你
We can help with that.
魯索，你可以走了
Russo, you're free to go.
- 不過就幾杯酒  - 就足以被攔下來
-It was just a few drinks.  -It was enough to get pulled over.
我沒有喝醉
I wasn't drunk-drunk.
- 你一個人？  - 對
-Were you alone?  -Yes.
- 看著我回答  - 看路
-Say it to my face.  -Watch the road.
- 看著我回答！  - 是，我一個人！
-Say it to my face!  -Yes, I was alone!
你不能一直這樣下去，彼得  夜路走多總會遇到鬼
You cannot keep doing this, Peter.  It's going to catch up with you.
我知道
I know.
傑弗遜晚宴  可以再安插兩個位子嗎？
Do you think we can arrange two more  at our table for the Jefferson Ball?
- 給誰？  - 霍本夫婦
-For whom?  -The Holburns.
- 你怎麼會要他們出席？  - 淨水創權需要她的獻金
-Why on earth would you want them there?  -I'm going to need her money for the CWl.
光是裁員還不夠
The staff cuts are just not enough.
我去跟瓦克斯談
I'll talk to Vasquez.
- 我們這如何？  - 很好
-How're we doing?  -Good.
很有進展，打鐵趁熱
Progress. Irons in the fire.
我喜歡打鐵
I like irons.
但更喜歡火熱
But I love fire.
好…
Yes...
- 你…  - 這提案根本是垃圾，唐納
-What are you...  -The bill is garbage, Donald.
增稅？禁止補助券？  聯邦監管？
Tax increases? Ban on vouchers?  Federal oversight?
要我怎麼在委員會推動？
How do you expect me  to get that through a committee?
琳達要我寫時答應過我…
When Linda told me to write it,  she promised...
我相信她說了不少  別管他們承諾你什麼，唐納
I'm sure she said any number of things.  Forget what they promised you, Donald.
他們要你聯名是因為你夠份量
They want your name  because it carries weight.
我的名字跟的是我的想法
Well, my name comes with my ideas.
我明白，但你得講理啊
I understand,  but you've got to be reasonable.
這可不是大辯論
This isn't the Great Debate.
重點是要通過有意義的改革
It's about passing meaningful reform.
或許不能盡如你意  但你得讓我幫你
Maybe not everything you would hope.  But help me help you.
我需要更多時間
That's going to take time.
這些點子，我思考了很…
Those ideas, I've been developing them for...
若你需要時間  我可以幫你緩一下
If it's time you need, I will buy you time.
但你必須答應我  下次給我一些可行的提議
But you've got to promise me your next at bat  is gonna give me something I can work with.
好吧，法蘭，我盡量
Okay, Frank, I'll see what I can do.
好，唐納  你別因為這樣而氣餒
Good. And, Donald,  don't let this get you down.
我們一起努力  一定能勝過你25年來的成就
Together, we're going to do more  than you've been able to do in 25 years.
有兩件事物不合時宜
Two things are now irrelevant.
唐納布萊斯  和唐納布萊斯草擬的新提案
Donald Blythe  and Donald Blythe's new draft.
最後我還是得重寫
Eventually, I'll have to re-write  the bill myself.
我們的口號是向前衝
Forward, that is the battle-cry.
撇下理念與紙上談兵的將軍  一點用都沒有
Leave ideology to the arm-chair generals.  It does me no good.
沃克剛任命凱恩
Walker just nominated Kern.
要得到批准，路還長著呢
It's a long road to confirmation.
凱恩根本是乖乖牌
Kern is a boy scout.
沒有人是乖乖牌  連乖乖牌們都不是
Nobody's a boy scout. Not even Boy Scouts.
- 你有什麼把柄？  - 什麼都沒有
-What do you have?  -Absolutely nothing.
那你是在說什麼？
Then what are we talking about?
只有一個簡單的問題  你對這職位有興趣嗎？
Just asking a simple question,  does the job interest you?
你為何要攆走麥克？
Why would you want Michael gone?
凱西，我們可是並肩作戰多年
Cathy, you and I came up together.
外交委員會  需要一個可以合作的國務卿
The Foreign Affairs Committee  needs a secretary we can work with.
一個不怕大聲指出沃克錯誤的人
Someone who isn't afraid to stand up  to Walker when he's wrong.
我們需要你
We need you.
假設我有興趣
Let's assume I am interested.
我不想假設，我想要確認
I don't want to assume. I want to know.
2…好，2637
2... Okay. 2-6-3-7.
請稍候，喬伊邦斯
Please hold. Zoe Barnes.
地點由你決定
Anywhere you want.
我馬上到，我待會回你電話
On my way. I'll gonna have to call you back.
抱歉，我叫不到計程車  只好搭火車…
I'm so sorry. I couldn't catch a cab.  I had to take a train and l...
你離開我家之前
Just before you left my house.
想想，我們那時在聊什麼？
Think back. What were we discussing?
- 總統的立法議程  - 具體一點
-The president's legislative agenda.  -Specifically.
教育
Education.
- 我猜對了嗎？  - 邦斯小姐，請你試想
-Was I right?  -Do the math, Ms. Barnes.
- 他需要一個提案  - 由誰提呢？
-He needs a bill.  -Sponsored by?
- 你嗎？  - 再聰明一點
-You?  -Be smarter than that.
- 一個有份量的人  - 很好
-Somebody with legitimacy.  -Good.
誰在教育這塊舉足輕重？
And who screams "legitimacy" in Education?
- 唐納布萊斯？  - 正確
-Donald Blythe?  -Correct.
- 問題是…  - 他是增稅花錢的老派左派分子
-The problem is...  -He's an old-school tax-and-spend liberal.
沃克是以溫和黨競選
Walker ran as a moderate.
他會跟我談嗎？
You think Blythe would talk to me?
他不需要
He doesn't have to.
等等…
Wait...
我們遊走道德與法律邊緣  我是無所謂…
We're in a very gray area, ethically, legally,  which I'm okay with...
我真喜歡這幅畫，你呢？
I just love this painting, don't you?
我們現在可是同舟共濟，喬伊
We're in the same boat now, Zoe.
要小心別將船翻了  我只能救我們當中一人
Take care not to tip it over.  I can only save one of us from drowning.
盧卡斯
他週一將宣佈教育提議
He announces  his education initiative on Monday.
- 演說一半是…  - 我明白
-Half of the address is...  -I understand.
- 需要刪掉嗎？  - 沒問題，琳達
-Do we need to take it out?  -We're fine, Linda.
但你才剛叫他重寫
But you just got through saying  he has to start over.
布萊斯不是我挑的  是你的人選
I didn't choose Blythe. You did.
是你將他扔給我  要求我讓奇跡發生，我會的
You put him in my lap  and asked me to work a miracle, and I will.
有點信心嘛，琳達  讓我和唐納搞定這件事
Now, have a little faith, Linda.  Let me work with Donald on this.
我很清楚百日內能完成什麼
I know what can be accomplished  in 100 days.
- 好吧，法蘭，就靠你了  - 很好
-All right, Frank, we're counting on you.  -Good.
我倒是有件小事要勞煩你
Now, I do have a little favor to ask.
能否再給我兩張  傑弗遜晚宴跟我同桌的入場券？
Do you think I can get just two more tickets  for my table at the Jefferson Ball?
來一杯嗎？
Drink?
- 好啊，你有什麼？  - 威士忌，調酒
-Sure, what do you got?  -Whiskey. Blends.
你請我當然樂意
If you're offering.
費城一切還好嗎？
So, how are things  in the City of Brotherly Love?
- 還過得去  - 很好
-We're getting by.  -Good, good.
- 抱歉，我直接倒了，你是要…  - 這樣正好
-I'm sorry, I made that neat. Did you want...  -No, this is perfect.
你最近彷彿有些不負責任
So, it seems you've been a bit irresponsible.
- 什麼？  - 別裝傻了，彼得
-What?  -Don't play dumb with me, Peter.
去跟倫理委員會說吧
Save it for the ethics committee.
喝了吧，你現在需要點勇氣
Drink up,  you could use a little courage right now.
你不喝嗎？
You're not having one?
對我來說有點早
It's a bit early in the day for me.
是那晚的事嗎？
Is this about the other night?
你怎麼會知道？
How do you know about that?
我是黨鞭，這是我的職責
I'm the Whip. It's my job to know.
他們放了我一馬，不起訴我
Look, they let me off. There's no charges.
都搞定了
It's all taken care of.
說真的，彼得  你真覺得這種事會自己搞定嗎？
Honestly, Peter, do you really think  these things just take care of themselves?
你…
You...
就只有這次，法蘭  我對天發誓
It was just this one time, Frank.  I swear to God.
那你還真不把老天當回事  因為你我都知道這是謊言
Then you must hold God in very low esteem,  because we both know that's a lie.
嫖妓、吸毒、酒後駕車…
Solicitation, controlled substances,  driving under the influence...
你興趣還真不少
You've got quite a long list of hobbies.
你想要怎麼樣？
What is it you want?
你全然的忠誠
Your absolute, unquestioning loyalty.
當然
Always.
別誤會了我所謂的忠誠
Do not misunderstand  what I mean by loyalty.
法蘭，只要你有需要
Anything. Name it, Frank.
你看來太若無其事了
You seem far too relaxed.
我沒有
I'm not.
你不應該
You shouldn't be.
道格會再跟你連絡
Doug will be in touch.
等等，你跑哪去了？  我一直打給你
Hang on. Where have you been?  I've been calling you.
大伙都在忙就職典禮的事
Everybody's working double-time  on inauguration
你竟然給我搞失蹤…
and you just up and disappear...
等等
Hang on.
ERAAA草案
我再回你
Let me call you back.
- 你這哪來的？  - 問題錯誤
-Where did you get this?  -Wrong question.
正確的問題是  要多久才能上傳到官網？
The right question is  how quickly can we get it up on the site?
我要先給湯姆批准
I have to run this past Tom.
找法律部門來看  確定我們沒有違法
Let's get legal on this,  make sure we're not breaking any laws.
- 你不告訴我你的線民？  - 無可奉告
-You won't tell me your source?  -I can't do that.
- 好，但法律部門要是找到…  - 我明白
-Fine. But if legal finds even one...  -I understand.
需要多久時間？  這個應該立即上傳
How long do you think that will take?  We should get this online right away.
我才不打算掃瞄三百頁的文件
I'm not just going to scan  a 300-page document
然後傳上網，我們得先通過…
and put it up  before we've gone through every...
我已經確認了
I did that already.
- 整份文件？  - 從頭到尾
-The whole thing?  -Cover to cover.
我有摘錄，還有分析  三千字準備編輯
I've got excerpts. Analysis.  3,000 words ready for editing.
你先看一遍
You start going over that.
讓美術部做一些圖表  千萬別客氣
Get graphics working on tables, charts,  the whole nine yards.
珍妮！
Janine!
- 什麼立場，四個字？  - 極左派
-What's the angle, five words?  -Far left of center.
- 這才三個字  - 非常左派
-That's four.  -Very far left of center.
能讓沃克緊張嗎？
Enough to put Walker on his heels?
何止緊張，讓他發狂
Fuck his heels. This will put him on his ass.
怎樣？
What's up?
我們拿到一份總統府的教育提案
We've got a copy  of the administration's education bill.
你跟喬伊合作背景故事
You're going to work with Zoe,  do background copy.
- 喬伊邦斯？  - 在這
-Zoe Barnes?  -Right here.
全力支援她
Whatever she needs.
- 不是該由我寫…  - 她已經寫好了
-Shouldn't I be writing the...  -She wrote it already.
我要你重寫再重寫，你幫她
And I want you to re-write it,  then re-write it again. You'll help her.
- 湯姆，我才是主要政治記者  - 快去
-Tom, I'm your chief political correspondent.  -Go.
- 我明天就要  - 但我需要專注在就職典禮的事
-I want this by tomorrow.  -But I need to focus on the inauguration.
這更重要
This is more important.
快開始吧
Let's get started.
…我將會忠實執行  美國總統府的職責
...that I will faithfully execute the office  of President of the United States.
「…我將會忠實執行…」
"...that I will faithfully execute the office... "
權力就像房地產，地段最重要
Power is a lot like real estate.  It's all about location, location, location.
離中心地帶越近，房價就越高
The closer you are to the source,  the higher your property value.
幾世紀後  當人們看到這個片段
Centuries from now,  when people watch this footage,
會看到誰在鏡頭邊緣微笑？
who will they see  smiling just at the edge of the frame?
「願神助我」
"So help me God. "
恭喜
Congratulations.
現場直播  總統就職典禮
今天講的不是今後的四年
Today is not about the next four years.
是往後的四十年
It's about the next four decades.
你們托信於我
You've placed your faith in me,
我將此信任  轉托於我們的孩子們
and I, in turn,  choose to place that faith in our children.
兒童是開啟國家未來的鑰匙
Our children  are the key to this nation's future,
所以總統府的首要任務
and that's why the first order of business  for this administration
就是完整的教育改革提案
will be a comprehensive  education reform bill
將改善、補助  並加強我國的學府
to properly fix, finance  and strengthen our nation's schools.
總統就職典禮
我向你們承諾
And I pledge to you,
在就職百日內
we will have that bill  on the floor of the Congress
會將提案提交國會
within the first 100 days  of this administration.
真是感謝你讓這一切成真
It was so nice of you to make this possible.
- 你打給我時我簡直…  - 別提了
-When you called me, I was...  -Not another word.
我今年大概  沒機會參加飛盤比賽了
I'm going to miss out  on my ultimate Frisbee league this season.
我說真的
No, I'm serious.
我們預算委員會  跟財務部可是宿敵呢
A few of us on Budget have quite a rivalry  going with the guys on Finance.
競賽可是很激烈的
It's fierce. We get physical.
有人敢擋我得分  我可不會對他客氣的
Anybody gets between me and that goal line,  I will take that sucker down.
唐納，我到處找你
Donald, I've been looking for you  everywhere, maestro.
- 是喔  - 我來幫你
-Yeah.  -Let me help you out there.
我很喜歡你的新草案
I really like the work  you've done on the new draft.
向前邁進一大步  我們將共同創造歷史
It's a big step forward.  We're going to make history together.
謝謝鼓勵，法蘭斯
Thanks for your encouragement, Francis.
聽著，關於補助金的事  我有些看法…
Listen, I've got some ideas about subsidies...
凱薩琳！你等等，唐納
Catherine! Hold on to that thought, Donald.
你真美
Don't you look stunning.
南方姑娘脫掉鄉巴佬裝
We Southern girls clean up well
換上設計師服裝  打扮起來也不錯
when we get out of our Daisy Dukes  and into some Vera Wang.
我們南方男孩不擅言詞  但可會跳舞了
And we Southern boys are slow  with our words, but we're fast on our feet.
- 我有這榮幸嗎？  - 當然
-May I have the honor?  -You most certainly may.
弗萊迪  烤肉舖
- 早安，弗萊迪  - 早，法蘭
-Morning, Freddy.  -Mornin', Frank.
- 生意怎麼樣？  - 還可以
-How's tricks?  -Can't kick.
- 要進去坐嗎？  - 不，就坐外面吧
-You want to go on in?  -No, why don't you set me up outside?
外面？很冷耶
Outside? It's freezing out here.
冷點比較有精神
Well, a little cold never hurt anybody.
你開心就好，法蘭
Anything you say, Frank.
馬上來
It'll be right up.
我唯一的放縱就是烤豬小排  就算是早上7點半
My one guilty pleasure is a good rack of ribs.  Even at 7:30 in the morning.
這地方只有我一人  弗萊迪有時還特別為我開店
I have the whole place to myself.  Freddy sometimes opens up just for me.
我老家南卡羅來納州  大家都很窮
Where I come from in South Carolina, people  didn't have two pennies to rub together.
烤豬小排是種奢侈，就像…
A rack of ribs was a luxury, like...
教育提案  非常左派
龐大預算與左派掛勾
提案擴大聯邦控制  喬伊邦斯
…提早過聖誕
...Christmas in July.
沃克就職  承諾教育大改革
網路簡直塞爆了
This web traffic is absolutely crazy.
…藍色豐田房車  疑似撞死家犬後逃逸
...blue Camry's wanted in connection  to a canine hit-and-run.
- 這是你的車嗎？  - 怎麼了？
-Hey, is this your car?  -What's going on?
- 要再來一份嗎，法蘭？  - 還是不要了
-You want seconds, Frank?  -I better not.
不，弗萊迪，再給我一份
Tell you what, Freddy. Yes, I will.
今天特別餓
I'm feeling hungry today.